Today, while cleaning the play button, I remembered
that schools are going to open from tomorrow, so I
went straight from home and ran to the ATM and brother, I had earned
income from YouTube, so I had to withdraw money
because I had to buy things for going to school.  First of all
we reached the clothes
shop and from there I bought my school dress
which I really enjoyed wearing.
After that we went to buy good shoes and
while buying the shoes I was very confused.
Then I liked these shoes.  Then
wearing it I did a little cat walk and
I really enjoyed getting a discount from the uncle whose shoes were shining and on the
way I saw a pani puri
stall and I had to eat pani puri anyway and
we had just bought half the stuff so we went to
buy a bag and I liked this bag and after paying for it
we went straight to the stationery shop
and told bhaiya the names of all the subjects and
bhaiya quickly took out the copies and books and gave them to me
seeing which I started feeling dizzy
because this time the time for studying is a bit
more.  Then we left straight for home
with our brother.  So look at the detective dogs
and the cute kids waving us goodbye
and I was exhausted after carrying so much stuff.